tips2secure.com 2018-03-20

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tips2secure collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [www.tips2secure.com](http://www.tips2secure.com/) website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Tips2secure

**Your Privacy**

We will not sell, trade, give, etc., the statistics that we collect on our site to any third party, without your express permission. The data that we collect is not mined or used for marketing purposes in any way. The data that we collect is used solely for purposes of web metrics and traffic analysis by Tips2secure.com. Be assured that safeguarding the contents of our website traffic is our priority. The following statement sets our privacy policy.

**Cookies**

This blog uses Cookies and web server log files to collect info, such as date and time of your visit. Cookies are also used by Advertisers to show relevant ads to readers.

**We may collect Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**How we use collected Information**

Tips2secure may collect and use Users personal information to improve our Site, better users experience. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

**Security**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Authorship of Contents**  
**  
**All the articles pulished here are written with the help of Tips2secure Team. Copying the articles and content from this website is strictly prohibited. If we found someone violating our these terms then he/she will be punished under DMCA complaint.  
We allow to use links of our website and posts in your own articles and blogs.

**Comment Policy**

You have full rights to comment your real and genuine views on any of posts published on Tips2secure. Vulgar and hating comments will be removed without any prior notice. If you have some negative and criticizing points about the programs or product reviews posted on Tips2secure.com, you can comment but you also have to provide some proofs to prove your points within 24 hours or your comment will be considered as spam and removed.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, please e-mail [kumarsluck0001@gmail.com](mailto:privacy@Opentracker.net)

**Links**

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**This document was last updated on 26-11-2015**
